legislation.gov.uk 2018-11-21

# Privacy Notice

## Search Legislation

Title: _(or keywords in the title)_

Year:

Number:

Type:

## Introduction

The legislation.gov.uk website is managed by The National Archives, a non-ministerial department and publisher for the UK Government and for England and Wales. The website is operated on behalf of the Data Controller, the National Archives (TNA) under a contract with The Stationery Office (TSO) who is the Data Processor.

## Information we collect about you online

When you visit this website, our Contractor, TSO, collects website usage information and information about your computer and internet connection, including your computer’s IP address, the type and version of browser (such as Internet Explorer 7 or Firefox 3.6) and operating system you use, your internet domain and, if you arrived at legislation.gov.uk via a link from another website, the URL of the linking page.

This information is used to ensure, as far as is practical, that the legislation site is compatible with the browsers and operating systems used by most of our visitors. It is also used for research to improve our understanding of customer needs in developing the website. The National Archives processes this information in order to provide you with access to the legislation.gov.uk website, in exercise of the function of a Minister of the Crown. 

The results of all such research and analysis will be presented as anonymous or aggregated information and will not reveal any personal facts about individual users. The contract with TSO ensures that data is managed securely, and not shared with any third parties.

As a general rule, the legislation.gov.uk site does not use cookies. Cookies are used when the site runs banner adverts – for user surveys or for job advertisements for The National Archives.

Find out about cookies here and how and why we use them.

## Your rights

You have certain rights in relation to the personal information we collect about you. These include the right to request access to your personal information, to request that it is erased, or that its processing is restricted, or that any inaccurate personal information is rectified though there are exemptions if the information is required by law to be published. You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information, or in some circumstances to obtain a copy of the personal information in machine readable format. Any such request should be submitted in writing to our customer service team. 

You also have the right to complain about the use your personal information to the local supervisory authority, which in the UK is the Information Commissioner’s Office (www.ico.org.uk). 

You can contact them by calling 0303 123 1113. Or go online to www.ico.org.uk/concerns (opens in a new window; please note we can't be responsible for the content of external websites). 

Or you can write to them at: 

Information Commissioner's Office,   
Wycliffe House,   
Water Lane,   
Wilmslow Cheshire,   
SK9 5AF 

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

The Privacy Notice will be reviewed from time to time to take account of changes to our operations or practices and, further, to make sure it remains appropriate to any changes in law, technology and the business environment. Any personal information held will be governed by the most current Privacy Notice. 

## The National Archives’ Data Protection Officer

For more information please contact our Data Protection Officer, Linda Stewart, at

The National Archives,  
Kew,  
Surrey,  
TW9 4DU.

Email addresses follow the format: firstname.lastname@nationalarchives.gov.uk.
